There's no going back to normal.
Leave the World Behind is a drama, mystery,
thriller film directed by Sam Esmail.
A family's getaway to a luxurious rental home takes an ominous turn when a
cyberattack knocks out their devices—and two strangers appear at their door.
Amanda Sandford, played by Julia Roberts.
Clay Sandford, played by Ethan Hawke.
G.H. Scott, played by Mahershala Ali.
Ruth Scott, played by Myha'la.
Rose Sandford, played by Farrah Mackenzie.
Archie Sandford, played by Charlie Evans.
Leave the World Behind is a 2023 American apocalyptic psychological
thriller film written and directed by Sam Esmail.
It is based on the 2020 novel of the same name by Rumaan Alam.
The film stars Julia Roberts, Mahershala Ali, Ethan Hawke, Myha'la, and Kevin Bacon as they attempt to make sense of the
gradual breakdown in phones, television, and other regularly used technology which points to a potential cataclysm.
Leave the World Behind had its world premiere at
the AFI Fest on October 25, 2023.
It was released in select theaters on November 22, 2023, before its
streaming release by Netflix on December 8, 2023.
It received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
blackout, crisis, vacation, deer.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.